<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><reviews><item><userImages>https://s3-media0.fl.yelpcdn.com/photo/CyP8Qc3DESUM2ksbgGvHjQ/60s.jpg</userImages><username>Jennifer M.</username><rating>5</rating><reviewDate>4/27/2019</reviewDate><reviewContent>Amazing place and great customer service. Is a nice place to go and enjoy the view. The food is good and amazing Margaritas. I will come back soon.</reviewContent><title/></item><item><userImages>https://s3-media0.fl.yelpcdn.com/photo/MgMXRN3fVWPkHTwL4kbnqg/60s.jpg</userImages><username>Angela K.</username><rating>3</rating><reviewDate>9/23/2018</reviewDate><reviewContent>If you're going here for the food, forget it. It's still fun if you go with the right people and want to enjoy views of Manhattan.It's $10 (plus some change) for admission onto the boat. The boat leaves promptly on schedule, so don't plan on going with stragglers! The good thing is, if part of your group doesn't make it, they can always hop on later and you can stay on the boat as long as it's operational.Service is good - we had a large party and not only were they able to accommodate us in terms of space, but the servers were on top of it, even we had random people joining us here and there.Food, as mentioned, is meh. Lobster roll was super bland and not worth what I paid. I feel bad that this was my friend's first lobster roll experience. Truffle fries were decent.Probably wouldn't go again if going for lobster rolls, but perhaps another trip for social reasons.</reviewContent><title/></item><item><userImages>https://s3-media0.fl.yelpcdn.com/photo/_XtM3481SGnYWgxHAUALiQ/60s.jpg</userImages><username>Sam K.</username><rating>2</rating><reviewDate>8/1/2018</reviewDate><reviewContent>The idea of this place encompasses everything I love: bars, boats, sunsets, lobster rolls.. but in going there it proved the ultimate disappointment.Upon arriving, there is a bar to grab drinks before the boat arrives- a mob people in front of us, 1 bartender, gave up on getting drinks there.When we got on the boat, every table is marked with a reserved sign, but they remove it as they seat you, so that was confusing. But you realize then it's not really a social bar setting, it's a seated dinner with table service.Drinks- a group of 4 of us ordered the Watermelon Mule pitcher, which was syrupy, sugary and not drinkable. The $55 pitcher went nearly untouched as we all had to reorder new drinks.Food- apps ordered were truffle fries and shark bites. Shark bites are nothing more than fish sticks that you eat from the freezer isle of the grocery store when your little..We all went with Lobster rolls (how could you not?) which came on soggy bread and a bag of chips were nothing to talk about really.. so I guess what I'd say is get one because that's probably what you went for, but don't have high expectations.More disappointing than the drinks was the boating situation: you can get on board 45 min before the boat takes of (in our case we went for the 7:30 sail time and boarded at 6:45). You sit there as you wait to sail, and then when the boat takes off it does a quick 45 min loop on the west side and then goes right back and docs for another 45 min. So essentially you sit docked for more time than you sail. And the ploy is, you can stay on as long as you want, but why would you want to stay really? We left as soon as the boat docked at 8:15 and cut out losses.Lastly, the price: groan. Don't get me wrong, you should have every expectation that a place like this will cost you, but the 4 of us each walked out spending $70/person on bad drinks, a replacement drinks, 2 mediocre apps and a soggy lobster roll.So to sum things up, I don't recommend it! There are better options for the bar/boat/sunset seekers.</reviewContent><title/></item><item><userImages>https://s3-media0.fl.yelpcdn.com/photo/DUjZE35eZcaCzOaRRlC8Bw/60s.jpg</userImages><username>Alexis G.</username><rating>2</rating><reviewDate>8/17/2017</reviewDate><reviewContent>I found this place through a family member and it was a good experience!! We got on the boat around 7 pm and it was super crowded. Some tables have reserved on them, but I suggest still asking to take one if no one has by the time they leave the dock. The upper deck is filled with people and it is nearly impossible to wait to find a seat.As for the food, it wasn't bad. Not the best I've ever had though and it is really pricey. I had the clam chowder and their main lobser entree. The soup was by far one of the bests I had ever had. However, it comes in a small cup and it does cost more than it should in my opinion. The lobster was amazing. It was a whole lobster on top of a bed of potatoes and some veggies and a whole corn. The veggies were okay. Might be just me, but I did not really like them together with the lobster. The corn was pretty good, could use some more flavor though. They also only give one lemon for a whole lobster.Overall, the experience was cool because they take you out on the river for some time and the view was amazing! You get to be in the middle of NJ and NY. The servers were nice, but always in a rush because it was so busy for them. Understandable. This a good place to try, but I can probably get better food with a better price than this.</reviewContent><title/></item><item><userImages>https://s3-media0.fl.yelpcdn.com/photo/jhu93TPcos-Rep9SkP--kg/60s.jpg</userImages><username>Chris S.</username><rating>4</rating><reviewDate>7/18/2018</reviewDate><reviewContent>I planned a summer outing for my team on the NRLC and it did not disappoint.  Keep in mind, this was a planned group purchase so my experience might be a smidge different than just popping in for dinner/drinks.The boat company gave me 3 options which basically accounted for a flat rate head count that included food packages and/or drinks.  We went with a package that included lobster rolls, burgers, veggie burgers, fries, and salad.  The food was amazing - oddly enough the house Italian dressing for the salad stands out in my memory the most - but again it was all so good.Also - if you plan ahead, they will give you a great spot on top the boat to make the experience all the better going up and down the Hudson.  Overall, my coworkers loved it and I highly highly recommend doing it at least once.Just make sure if you have a pre-planned time that your whole group is ON TIME! (the captain had to hold the boat for 5 mins because of a couple late teammates of mine)</reviewContent><title/></item><item><userImages>https://s3-media0.fl.yelpcdn.com/photo/y9SxjRQ4pqmYDB3XbnfpBg/60s.jpg</userImages><username>Angela C.</username><rating>2</rating><reviewDate>8/15/2018</reviewDate><reviewContent>Pros: Great food, really sweet waitress, it's a boat.Cons:Really disappointed with the seating situation.During the second sailing around 7pm more people boarded and they were seated within my reserved, guaranteed area that I had paid for. We tried to explain that this was reserved, but the boat staff insisted on seating people in the area that I had paid for. It seemed they had over sold the number of tickets to get on board and didn't think about seating.Around 8 people were seated in my area that I paid for. It made the situation really awkward and they were literally sitting next to the food / drinks that we had also ordered. At one point I believe a few guests outside of our party were drinking and eating our food. Really unacceptable since I thought the space and food was guaranteed for only my party.</reviewContent><title/></item><item><userImages>https://s3-media0.fl.yelpcdn.com/photo/PWnsnLPRu6dnVI7oFSTJxQ/60s.jpg</userImages><username>Natalie S.</username><rating>5</rating><reviewDate>6/7/2018</reviewDate><reviewContent>I read about this on Yelp and because there were a lot of iffy reviews, I was apprehensive. My biggest concern was that it was going to be a tourist, crowded shitshow. But I wanted to be on a boat and this particular boat was close to my friend's house where we were staying.This is how it works: there were sailings the Saturday we went at 6pm, 7:30pm and 9pm. You pay $10 for a wristband that gets you into the boat. That is good all night so if you board for the 6pm sailing, you can go back and forth until they kick you off. You kinda have to flag a waiter down if you want service because I suspect they're used to people paying the $10 and just sitting. There are three (or four?) levels. We easily got a table for our party of 5 on the top level.Drinks were $15 a cocktail. Buckets of beer were not a bad price but for the life of me, I can't remember exactly how much ($32 for 5 or 6? Can you tell I don't drink beer?).The food was ok. I got a pound of crab legs for $30. That's pretty ok pricing. Were they the best crab legs I've ever had? Well, no. But they were just fine. That's pretty much what everyone else at my table said about their lobster rolls. They were very acceptable lobster rolls for a very acceptable price considering we were sitting on a boat while eating them.The service was friendly and whenever we waived someone down for more drinks or condiments or whatever, they were accommodating.This place exceeded my expectations. The rest of my party said the same thing. They are local and said they would bring people to do this again, absolutely.</reviewContent><title/></item><item><userImages>https://s3-media0.fl.yelpcdn.com/photo/cXwFNb_10txz7H_ot6ZALA/60s.jpg</userImages><username>Shana C.</username><rating>5</rating><reviewDate>10/4/2019</reviewDate><reviewContent>So romantic if you go at night. My boyfriend and I enjoyed our time here. You can't beat the prices!! The food was really good. I ordered the whole lobster with potatoes and corn and a two sangria's to wash it down. I also ordered the lobster Mac and Cheese squares with I didn't really care for (no lobster meat visible). Definitely a great date night experience. Dress code is cute but casual.</reviewContent><title/></item><item><userImages>https://s3-media0.fl.yelpcdn.com/photo/E3P3lXLZ73A4HQoX6BdWjg/60s.jpg</userImages><username>Jenny N.</username><rating>3</rating><reviewDate>4/21/2017</reviewDate><reviewContent>Sailing season just started for 2017! I can with two friends tonight. It wasn't the warmest night. 40-50, we were of three parties on the boat. The boat departed at 7pm and took us up the Hudson for an hour.- $10 admission to board now.- no hot drinks on the menu (although you can request hot water)- service is attentive and always checks on us.- cruise felt rather short- we all ordered lobsters, they were good.Overall assessment, go for the experience once but is it worth it? Good to take friends from out of town but I think it's overpricedNote; the boat is rockier than I expected.</reviewContent><title/></item><item><userImages>https://s3-media0.fl.yelpcdn.com/photo/1ol8xxhtgGvesCEV_LN4yw/60s.jpg</userImages><username>Phaedra S.</username><rating>3</rating><reviewDate>9/7/2019</reviewDate><reviewContent>It pains me to give any seafood spot 3 stars but the service was the root. I came here for my birthday and the waiter disappeared for half an hour. We flagged three different people down just to find him. Once we ordered he disappeared again.The food ended up coming before the drinks and we had to flag 3 more people down just to get the drinks. Overall it's great place for a tourist but do not come here hungry or expecting to get the best service. It has great views of manhattan the cruise itself is about 45 minutes unfortunately the service was horrible.</reviewContent><title/></item><item><userImages>https://s3-media0.fl.yelpcdn.com/photo/JAxdh62cmyxvZxCjWKchNA/60s.jpg</userImages><username>Demishia O.</username><rating>3</rating><reviewDate>6/2/2018</reviewDate><reviewContent>The view was beautiful. We went on around 6:00pm. It was great it wasn't crowded. It was just right. We had the main lobster roll. It was average price and some drinks. It was good. You are allowed to stayed on do once the 7:00pm crowd came on it was crowded. They were all around our table. We also shared our table with another couple. So if your looking for something private don't go in the evening. The scenery was beautiful.</reviewContent><title/></item><item><userImages>https://s3-media0.fl.yelpcdn.com/photo/tBQeEDeN16yEefBG2gaH_w/60s.jpg</userImages><username>Weich Y.</username><rating>4</rating><reviewDate>5/29/2018</reviewDate><reviewContent>Their lobster rolls are fresh and delicious. I also love their various other appetizers like popcorn shrimp and fries - perfect for sharing and perfect for eating on a boat with cold drinks for those that are wondering, this cruise does not go down to the Statue of Liberty. But the views of the Hudson are great!</reviewContent><title/></item><item><userImages>https://s3-media0.fl.yelpcdn.com/photo/WRfln47r9PU5-jz4bWuyog/60s.jpg</userImages><username>Elizabeth K.</username><rating>5</rating><reviewDate>6/27/2018</reviewDate><reviewContent>I surprised my husband with an afternoon on the boat, that involved drinks and food. We absolutely loved it, even our 20 month old son had the time of his life and was able to take a nap.The lobster rolls were amazing, and the oysters were so fresh! A little pricey overall, but that's a given when you get to enjoy drinks, food and sail the Hudson. The staff are very friendly, and sweet.A few things to keep in mind before going... this is a first come first serve establishment, and as long as you have a boarding pass, you do not have to get off the boat. From what I saw the 2nd and 3rd levels got pretty busy, and people had to wait. My family and I were on the first level deck which was perfect.We spent about 7 hours there, and enjoyed every minute of it. All in all, a great way to spend the afternoon if you want to just eat and relax!</reviewContent><title/></item><item><userImages>https://s3-media0.fl.yelpcdn.com/photo/LeLnT1tQcZ7CWfETNRNzZQ/60s.jpg</userImages><username>Edwin M.</username><rating>4</rating><reviewDate>6/24/2019</reviewDate><reviewContent>Great river cruise . I should have given them 5 star if drink is a little bit cheaper . But overall great experience.</reviewContent><title/></item><item><userImages>https://s3-media0.fl.yelpcdn.com/photo/mnjuiKA5ImDFdVFPR6hCSw/60s.jpg</userImages><username>Kit C.</username><rating>4</rating><reviewDate>7/31/2018</reviewDate><reviewContent>We drove here and parked our car at the public parking by this pier 81, very reasonable with a flat rate of $35 for the day till midnight. Two minutes walk to NRLC. Cost $10 per person for boarding pass. The boat is a little dated, was a bit disappointed of the conditions. Got ourselves a seat on the top deck, boat left for the forty five minutes ride on the Hudson right on schedule. We order a lobster roll to share, we had better for the price of $22. A dozen oyster which was very fresh. A side of Fries and two beers.The bill came to $90. We did this as s test run before we bring our friends who will be visiting from Las Vegas. I think it's quite a good experience for tourists. We will definitely bring them.</reviewContent><title/></item><item><userImages>https://s3-media0.fl.yelpcdn.com/photo/zj00N6W44QFXJ-EdVWBL_Q/60s.jpg</userImages><username>Charles M. W.</username><rating>4</rating><reviewDate>10/7/2019</reviewDate><reviewContent>Not the sightseeing excursion I thaught I would be embarking. The boat is slated for 2 hour seating even though you are permitted to stay aboard for continuous sailings. I realize I came aboard at the end of the sailing season and the vessel was not crowded but it appeared we sat at the dock a long time while they waited for perspective passengers before pushing off. During the two hour time slot we only went on a half hour cruise up river. The food was good especially for being no frills seafood. Time sailing on the river could have been longer but overall I can say been there done that!</reviewContent><title/></item><item><userImages>https://s3-media0.fl.yelpcdn.com/photo/YyKwtEvKoIqfCm2CKmbVUw/60s.jpg</userImages><username>Christopher L.</username><rating>1</rating><reviewDate>5/28/2019</reviewDate><reviewContent>Went for my birthday. Sat at a table for 50 minutes with no service. Asked a server to please help us he said "I'm not your server but I'll get yours" still nobody came. Asked another worker who said "someone will come to you eventually". Told him that the table next to us got there after us and already had their food and drinks but he walked away smirking. Eventually went to the bar and waited in line for 15 minutes to buy our drinks and walk them over myself. When a server finally realized nobody was helping us (now way over an hour in) he didn't apologize or ask if there was anything he could do for us. So disappointing.</reviewContent><title/></item><item><userImages>https://s3-media0.fl.yelpcdn.com/assets/srv0/yelp_styleguide/514f6997a318/assets/img/default_avatars/user_60_square.png</userImages><username>Lauren J.</username><rating>4</rating><reviewDate>9/21/2019</reviewDate><reviewContent>oh my god found the prefect place the lobster Mac and cheese balls they where amazing !!!I had ordered 2 of these for my self and left nothing :)Would adjust customer service a bit.... from all employees. No one looks happy.Napkins and utensils/ cups flew off into the water by accident ... I would recommend they invest in a more eco friendly disposables since they are right on the water and travel in water. I'm sure it happens to others. The thought of me adding to pollution by involuntary littering haunts me. There must be something they could do ..</reviewContent><title/></item><item><userImages>https://s3-media0.fl.yelpcdn.com/photo/DbhVIuE5kyPTF11RCruSdw/60s.jpg</userImages><username>joe m.</username><rating>3</rating><reviewDate>7/27/2019</reviewDate><reviewContent>Not nearly as bad as I thought it was going to be a great view of the city very short ride but for one time was worth it lobster roll was good but small pretty much expected that enjoyed it</reviewContent><title/></item><item><userImages>https://s3-media0.fl.yelpcdn.com/photo/598LHKPKIJbTeznlcmUZQw/60s.jpg</userImages><username>Steve N.</username><rating>5</rating><reviewDate>1/2/2018</reviewDate><reviewContent>(09/01/2017) Still a 5-star destination because I go out of my way to while away summer happy hours here. The cruising seems to have more structure than I remember from previous visits. The boat leaves at specific times and the route is to 96 Street. On a recent Fri oysters were $3 each, very good; and a bottle of rose was $43.55. Spectacular views? Free.TIP good value for tourists and sightseersTIP you can still catch a car at the dock to go to dinner, and make your Lobster Boat cruise a Happy Hour(from August 2015) For all of its faults, I've made North River Lobster Company a destination for walking on a summer afternoon from the west 80s twice, so it must ultimately rate 5 stars. The food is a little pricey, the wine's a fair deal (sauvignon blanc for the GF, 10), beer's a little steep (Pacifico, 8) and not draft, but the whole package is unbeatable on a nice day. Get there at a reasonable hour, find some seats in the sun, and enjoy the occasional cruise to 72nd or 79th Street, eat a fair meal, enjoy some bottles of beer and wine, and you'll probably be happier than you expect. Here's some tips and bonuses.BONUS - great outdoor seatingTIP - counter service - you order at the bar, pay, and you get a flag for the table so the server can bring you your food; you carry your own drinks</reviewContent><title/></item></reviews>