<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><reviews><item><userImages>https://s3-media0.fl.yelpcdn.com/photo/lJb5LUWM3Q_tzLkcWAko3A/60s.jpg</userImages><username>Denise M.</username><rating>4</rating><reviewDate>11/13/2019</reviewDate><reviewContent>north river lobster company is such a cute find on the hudson river! for locals, this is not a huge attraction as it used to be free of charge. now, there is a $10 entry fee per person.i think the concept of this is great, you get to ride around a nice scenery for about an hour and talk with friends. it would be more fun if you are over 21 as they have a happy hour special.you can order food and alcohol while on the boat. we got lobster rolls, mac and cheese, fish and chips, and a few other small food items. there is nothing too special about the food or the ride, besides being on a peaceful boat ride on the hudson.i think it was a nice place to have in new york city, as boats are not as typical for this type of environment. we even got to see people kayaking on the hudson!overall - give it a try if you are in the area, you can visit the vessel afterward too! they dock the boat every hour or so, super nice in the summer.</reviewContent><title/></item><item><userImages>https://s3-media0.fl.yelpcdn.com/photo/KXV3uYaVj4ZtjElusW3umw/60s.jpg</userImages><username>Jess G.</username><rating>3</rating><reviewDate>10/28/2019</reviewDate><reviewContent>It's only open during the warmer months. You have to pay entry to get on the boat, like some kind of cover charge.The boat does go down the Hudson and circle back to dock so people can leave or get onto the boat. Either pay for one time entry or a full season pass. I got the full season pass and I'm not sure why I did because I hate midtown and I'm never here unless friends make plans up here.We split the Shelley - some gigantic 28" inch lobster roll. It was good and meaty. Not sure if I'd come back for lobster because there are a lot of other options for lobster in the city without a cover charge but I would come back with friends or to show people from out of town that nyc has a lobster boat because it is unique.</reviewContent><title/></item><item><userImages>https://s3-media0.fl.yelpcdn.com/photo/nYkxv9qS_eETwz4uRMF43w/60s.jpg</userImages><username>Cristina G.</username><rating>4</rating><reviewDate>8/14/2019</reviewDate><reviewContent>I think some of the reviews on here are a little harsh. Is the food mind-blowing? Absolutely not. But it's pretty good. And you get to eat and drink on a boat. Consider the entire experience as a whole before passing too much judgement.FYI, this is a cashless experience. Everything from your $10pp entrance fee to the drinks will require a credit or debit card, which I kinda like. I haven't carried cash since 2014 so I'm happy this place caught on lol.Our group of 15 had trouble getting outdoor seating since our party was so large and we didn't want to pay to reserve a space, so we sat inside for our meal and opted to go outside for another "cruise" to enjoy some drinks. This wasn't the worst thing considering it was pretty hot outside. Onto the food...Chances are you're here for the lobster. I definitely was. I went with the Bacon Lobster Roll served with thick-cut bacon, lettuce, and tomato on a potato roll with a bag of chips and coleslaw on the side. There was a ton of lobster and very little filler which was good, but I think the $24 was a bit pricey considering the bacon on the roll was ice cold and it didn't even come with fries- but again, I'm trying to consider the experience in it's entirety. The food was a solid 3.5 in my opinion, but not something I'd go out of my way to eat in the future.The drinks, again, were pricey but not terrible. I opted for the classic margarita ($16) which was good and STRONG. I was only able to drink 2 of these during our 2 hour cruise. Other folks in my group opted for other mixed drinks or beer from the buckets we ordered. The overall consensus was that the drinks were pretty decent.The service was awesome. Our waitress and some additional staff members were super patient in seating our group of 15 inside for a portion of our stay. They happily moved tables and chairs around for us to have 1 larger communal table so we could all dine family style. Our waitress was patient in taking our orders, brought our food out promptly, and even snagged us a reserved spot outside on the boat so we could enjoy our drinks in the sun. She really did go above and beyond for us which we all definitely appreciated.The views were awesome, naturally. Come here on a sunny day to enjoy the afternoon or in the evening to enjoy the sunset and I guarantee you'll be in for a treat.Definitely a cool experience, especially for groups. Not something I'd do more than once a summer so the summer pass wouldn't be worth it for me, but I'd visit again next year.</reviewContent><title/></item><item><userImages>https://s3-media0.fl.yelpcdn.com/photo/eB4X2UdUBURmsBNrJvY60w/60s.jpg</userImages><username>Daniel F.</username><rating>2</rating><reviewDate>7/23/2019</reviewDate><reviewContent>This lobster boat leaves the dock and comes back every hour or so. We were taken here by a vendor so we didn't actually pay for anything ourselves.Even with not having to pay for anything, we weren't pleased with the service or food. Numerous times we were asked to leave certain parts of the boat. Seems like we're restricted to certain areas based on what we paid for. This was not understood by all of the staff because we asked someone if we could go up and he said yes, but then someone else told us to go back down once we got upstairs. Very frustrating. We eventually went up again and nobody stopped us.. okWe also asked a few members of the crew what time the boat leaves the dock and were told different times from nearly all of them.The food.. well you'd think the lobster would be good. Nopeee! It was tough and super fishy. The lobster didn't taste fresh at all.The only good thing is the view and the free ride in a boat.</reviewContent><title/></item><item><userImages>https://s3-media0.fl.yelpcdn.com/photo/DqR-2OCX2CM4dNTC-QXhjw/60s.jpg</userImages><username>Anggie B.</username><rating>5</rating><reviewDate>7/29/2019</reviewDate><reviewContent>Having lobster, oyster and their community on a boat which sails through hudson river, sounds good?If yes, buy the ticket then!$10 for entrance only.Food is pricey, but this is expected as we pay for view.And food actually pretty good, it tastes fresh (maybe it is,since they have display inside).We can stay in the boat as long as we want1 more thing, my party was 8 people and the gratuity was automatically included (common thing in nyc).</reviewContent><title/></item><item><userImages>https://s3-media0.fl.yelpcdn.com/photo/GY9CqOYiuOmpAOclhyJnBA/60s.jpg</userImages><username>Isabel J.</username><rating>4</rating><reviewDate>6/6/2019</reviewDate><reviewContent>It was a warm Saturday afternoon and my husband and I were looking for a place to have dinner by the water. After some search I found this gem.I purchased the tix through their site and use the code from Yelp to save $5 per tix which was amazing. Usually you have to pay $10 as a cover which it isn't horrible.You pay the cover to get on the boat which is sort of like a bar/restaurant that sails every hour hand half for 40 mins.Your tix is for the whole day so you can spend as much or little time there are you want.When we got on the boat we decided to check upstairs deck to see if we could find a place to seat.We were lucky enough to find two free seats.A server welcomed us and gave us some menus.I decided to have the original lobster roll and my husband got the bacon lobster roll. Also we ordered the lobster fried Mac n cheese balls to share.I have to say both rolls were delicious and very generous with the amount of lobster in each of them. Totally worth every penny.However I was a bit disappointed with the Mac n cheese balls. They were very tasty but didn't have a lot of lobster so I don't think they are worth $16.I can't remember the name of my drink but it was really good and plenty of alcohol.While we were eating we sailed towards uptown for 40 mins. Then you come back and dock for another 40 mins and then it sails again and so on.This is such a cool concept and I will for sure be coming back very soon.</reviewContent><title/></item><item><userImages>https://s3-media0.fl.yelpcdn.com/photo/lYISa27pww_iFkiBfJgT6A/60s.jpg</userImages><username>Sunshine M.</username><rating>5</rating><reviewDate>8/24/2019</reviewDate><reviewContent>Back home in NYC and made it a point to come back to my fave lobster boat. So yes, they charge $10 to get on. You buy the ticket on the dock ( around the corner from the dock bar) then you get a bracelet from the crew checking you in. Got onboard and went for a glass of white and ordered a lobster roll. Spoke with a manager and called him out on the (new) $10 charge. Comes down to this, inflation, costs and overhead. Gas is going up, it's NYC and things cost money. While talking with him, I noticed SEVERAL people enjoying the ride without food nor a cocktail. (So we're also paying for people who don't want to indulge) not saying you have tobut it is a lobster boat. It was nice getting a comp glass of wine as well. The same boat ride would usually cost $25+ without the option for food/ wine. Still enjoy this and still recommend it ! And the lobster roll was generous and delicious!</reviewContent><title/></item><item><userImages>https://s3-media0.fl.yelpcdn.com/photo/Uo8Z1_AsXatRYXZXHDoxgA/60s.jpg</userImages><username>Mej N.</username><rating>5</rating><reviewDate>9/6/2019</reviewDate><reviewContent>Celebrated another Birthday here past Sunday and it was simply brilliant ! My family and friends had an amazing time. The Manager Bayley remembered me from my last visit ( I'm fabulously unforgettable ) and was simply warm and wonderful !! We enjoyed a huge "Shelly" a massive long Lobster Roll packed with fresh and tasty lobster meat , oysters and of course several bottles of Rose ! Thank you Bayley and service team for all your efforts. We will be back before the season ends !!!</reviewContent><title/></item><item><userImages>https://s3-media0.fl.yelpcdn.com/photo/0OFe8cR09WqMu2aQ4bIcYw/60s.jpg</userImages><username>Florence V.</username><rating>4</rating><reviewDate>8/20/2019</reviewDate><reviewContent>Great food and drinks with a view. We ordered several platters for a group that comes with lobster rolls, wings, and fries. The boat loops back to the dock around every 40mins or so, so don't worry if you miss the boarding time. It takes about 20mins to redock but you can stay on the boat for as many "loops" as you like. Refreshing drinks like the watermelon mule is on the menu. We also did several rounds of the paddle shooters. There are several decks including the lower indoor deck in case it rains.</reviewContent><title/></item><item><userImages>https://s3-media0.fl.yelpcdn.com/photo/k5GqGLo3nzJkaYDM0FDIvw/60s.jpg</userImages><username>Stephanie D.</username><rating>3</rating><reviewDate>9/5/2019</reviewDate><reviewContent>The Lower East Side Roll was nothing to write home about, but the Deep Fried Lobster MAC &amp;amp; Cheese Cubes were AWESOME. If you want a seat outside make sure to come early as people are allowed to stay on the boat all day which is something we didn't know. Definitely great for drinks and a gorgeous view.</reviewContent><title/></item><item><userImages>https://s3-media0.fl.yelpcdn.com/photo/-NcVMAwyWi3BjzHAXtMXyg/60s.jpg</userImages><username>Anna F.</username><rating>4</rating><reviewDate>9/23/2019</reviewDate><reviewContent>I went here with coworkers for an outing last week. The food was quite good, especially the fries. Perfectly crispy on the outside yet still fluffy on the inside. The rose sangria was good as well. A very relaxing thing to do with friends or for a date! View is very nice as well. However I was a little confused on their happy hour options. Otherwise a great experience</reviewContent><title/></item><item><userImages>https://s3-media0.fl.yelpcdn.com/photo/AvweWIY0uZ_cfiGd9P-CpA/60s.jpg</userImages><username>JT T.</username><rating>4</rating><reviewDate>7/15/2019</reviewDate><reviewContent>Decided after so many years of calling NYC home that I'd finally try out the lobster boat I've heard people talk about. Either some people don't have taste glands or they completely are out of their mind if they're saying the lobster roll doesn't have any flavor! Despite the price of the roll itself, it's pretty amazing and packed full of lobster. I enjoyed the roll and kind of wish they had like a brick and mortar place to hit up. Costs around 10 bucks just to get on the boat so you're already spending some cash before you add in the food and alcohol (fairly expensive for alcohol). For me, once you've been on one boat going up and down the Hudson then you've seen it all. Seating is limited outdoors on the boat since it's a pretty popular venue, but if you can snag a seat then great!Overall I enjoyed it, but would love to get this lobster roll without having to pay to get on a boat.</reviewContent><title/></item><item><userImages>https://s3-media0.fl.yelpcdn.com/photo/hs2bsoQsGpUAXCn5riZJ7g/60s.jpg</userImages><username>Michael J.</username><rating>4</rating><reviewDate>10/2/2019</reviewDate><reviewContent>Nice scenery convenient parking right across from boatFood was ok but it's not for that it's for the viewPeace and cool breeze from the oceanWould go again</reviewContent><title/></item><item><userImages>https://s3-media0.fl.yelpcdn.com/photo/ceA5mRBalF18s8LGiCUcIg/60s.jpg</userImages><username>Keith C.</username><rating>4</rating><reviewDate>8/11/2019</reviewDate><reviewContent>Fun time that is really more about the experience than the ears. Food was very so-so, and drinks were overpriced, but you can't beat the views. Go with a group to get maximum enjoyment. Stay on for two rides, too, to get the most of your money. $10 to ride all day is pretty fantastic.</reviewContent><title/></item><item><userImages>https://s3-media0.fl.yelpcdn.com/photo/UlIC_eMRrYRyPqDntWwzzQ/60s.jpg</userImages><username>Aubri P.</username><rating>4</rating><reviewDate>6/14/2019</reviewDate><reviewContent>SO MUCH FUN! We came here a couple of days ago after we saw an ad online. And it was one of the best times ever! We missed happy hour by a couple of minutes, so yes it was EXTREMELY pricey.This place is great because of its location. We found the boat to be great. It was clean, the cushioned seats were so comfortable and being out on the water was so relaxing, it felt like a mini vacation! Yes the boat ride is a bit "short". I personally didn't have too much of a problem with it because we boarded 30 mins prior and felt like we were on the boat for sufficient time. The reason for the 4 stars is because of the overall value of this place. In terms of price for what we get-- it is very steep. If the prices were more pocket-friendly and reflected the portion/value of the food, then it would easily be an above average place. The service here was also great. As soon as we stepped on the boat we were greeted with smiles! I can't remember the last time I was treated like that in NYC.All in all, service is great, servers are amicable, and boat ride is relaxing. Food was really good. I had the lower east side roll and it was great! The lobster tasted super fresh, but again-- a bit tooo pricey for the portion we get. The drinks were good as well! Perfect amount of alcohol and good size! I would definitely recommend this if you are looking for a refreshing eating experience!</reviewContent><title/></item><item><userImages>https://s3-media0.fl.yelpcdn.com/photo/OE_8mUx8fntMSHTCAYznrg/60s.jpg</userImages><username>Andrew F.</username><rating>4</rating><reviewDate>7/4/2019</reviewDate><reviewContent>Seafood was fresh, views were great and it was a beautiful day, so couldn't ask for much more. While the bar/table service was a bit slow and the ride was a bit too fast, the overall experience was fun. Definitely worth checking out on a nice sunny day, especially if craving lobster!</reviewContent><title/></item><item><userImages>https://s3-media0.fl.yelpcdn.com/photo/wkS8O8go-O1XH6-3eszH7Q/60s.jpg</userImages><username>Yianni A.</username><rating>2</rating><reviewDate>8/11/2019</reviewDate><reviewContent>I've been meaning to visit your establishment and devour "the shelly" ever since I saw the promo video on Thrillist. I finally came today, only to be told that you're out for the day.HOW can you not anticipate your weekend bread needs, when you've put so much into advertising yourselves as the biggest lobster roll in the city? Such a disappointment. We ended having the classic, the truffle, and two beers; and paid about $80. Another twenty and I could've had a two foot lobster roll... if you had ordered enough bread.</reviewContent><title/></item><item><userImages>https://s3-media0.fl.yelpcdn.com/photo/bFcdmlQ-N2nQKb7mTGDZ6Q/60s.jpg</userImages><username>Desiree D.</username><rating>5</rating><reviewDate>9/6/2019</reviewDate><reviewContent>Happy Hour at the bar on the pier while you wait. i believe its mon - fri, 3 pm to 7.00 $20 classic lobster rolls. other apps are pretty much half off. $5 shots (casa amigos is one of them, i had 4!), $5 beers and $5 glasses of wine. They take cards - no min. FYI, they do not take cash anywhere on the boat! Happy hour is ONLY on the pier!$5 tickets to get on the boat if you choose "See available tickets" from you yelp app. comes to 7.50 after taxes and fees, youll be emailed the tickets. youll be given a wrist band and can go on and off as much as you please. since the boat ride itself is 20 to 25 mins, we ran off before happy hour was over to the bar on the pier and stacked up on drinks. keep in mind a shot is 12 to 15 on the boat, so this happy hour is WORTH IT.if youre looking for seats on the top, outdoor area, there arent as many as youd think. keep in mind large parties can reserve seating. however, grab a table while you can and youre welcome to walk around otherwise. bathrooms on every floor, and theres multiple areas to hang out on.the staff was great, friendly, and helpful. everything came out fairly quick too.onto the good shit...the classic lobster roll is good. honestly, its well worth the money. I prefer a warm buttered roll w/buttery lobster, but this style of roll was well worth the money and was very good. why? well, there is no filler. its an abundant amount of lobster meat, with very little mayo and seasoning. topped with some scallions. however, the lobster is cold. more like a chilled lobster salad. also, it comes on a challah style roll/loaf, thats buttered but not heated up. we ordered the shelly. for 99.00 you get 6 lobster rolls. its one huge loaf on a wooden board, they dont cut it up. make sure youre sober enough to cut it up evenly if youre with guests. for 25.00 a person, we each got basically a lobster roll and a half. it comes with a large bag of kettle cooked chips and a large plastic bin of coleslaw. coleslaw is okay, nothing to rave about. however, the lobster roll was good. its in my top 5 and mainly because of the amount of meat and no filler.boat ride goes up north towards the GW Bridge, takes 20 to 25 mins. which doesnt give you enough time to eat. hence why they allow you to stay on. i did 2 rides to the north and had enough time to eat, grab more drinks on the pier, snack, and hang out. beautiful sunset and clean boat.would come back in a heart beat and try the truffle lobster roll!</reviewContent><title/></item><item><userImages>https://s3-media0.fl.yelpcdn.com/photo/v0b94jdvBtEyZSV0F_9FUA/60s.jpg</userImages><username>Tracey A.</username><rating>4</rating><reviewDate>8/26/2018</reviewDate><reviewContent>"Where does this go?" my friend kept asking."Basically, nowhere" I kept replying, certain that a boat ride to nowhere was 100% better than another stroll up Manhattan's 100 degree sidewalks.And I was right.NRLC is docked on the Hudson, at Pier 81. At regular 90-minute intervals it takes off from the Pier, performs a 20-minute cruise up the Hudson, then turns around and retraces its route back to the dock. 45 minutes in all, then you're docked again for another 45 but your $10 boarding fee allows you to stay on as long as you wish.I was good for two trips and I enjoyed every minute once we were gliding through the water. The part where you're waiting to do just that, a bit less so.The best place to be (IMO) is the top deck but you'll need to get there early (or stick around for a second ride) to secure your seat.Servers are young and happy (think "first job") and they get the job done without pressure to order anything once on board. I only drank - so can't speak to the food (you're on a boat with beautiful city views; this doesn't usually bode well for food quality) - and found the Margaritas to be cool and refreshing though low on alcohol.Plan your trip around their happy hour (currently 4 - 7pm M/W/Th) and the whole experience gets a whole lot more attractive.Between the air temperature, the water, the boat, and the booze I expected this to be a SRO sort of activity but there's room enough for everybody here. No advance-purchase needed.I had fun on the NRLC boat, killing a few hours in the heat of the day.</reviewContent><title/></item><item><userImages>https://s3-media0.fl.yelpcdn.com/photo/CAojbgC0mdYEXDk5v1BXcw/60s.jpg</userImages><username>Andrea A.</username><rating>4</rating><reviewDate>5/5/2019</reviewDate><reviewContent>Ok I was there on a rainy day that turned sunny right when I got onboard. So no crowd, quick service and nice views of Manhattan. Query what happens on a warm sunny day...The boat ride lasts approx. 30 minutes and costs $10. The food onboard is a bit expensive ($24 the lobster roll, $9 a beer) but not too bad for NYC standards.</reviewContent><title/></item></reviews>