<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><reviews><codes><item>687214286</item><item>687168492</item><item>686590819</item><item>685890320</item><item>685694512</item><item>685584312</item><item>685187228</item><item>685187045</item><item>685129953</item><item>685106295</item></codes><dates><item>July 6, 2019</item><item>July 6, 2019</item><item>July 3, 2019</item><item>July 1, 2019</item><item>July 1, 2019</item><item>June 30, 2019</item><item>June 29, 2019</item><item>June 29, 2019</item><item>June 29, 2019</item><item>June 28, 2019</item></dates><ratingClasses><item>ui_bubble_rating bubble_50</item><item>ui_bubble_rating bubble_50</item><item>ui_bubble_rating bubble_50</item><item>ui_bubble_rating bubble_50</item><item>ui_bubble_rating bubble_50</item><item>ui_bubble_rating bubble_50</item><item>ui_bubble_rating bubble_50</item><item>ui_bubble_rating bubble_50</item><item>ui_bubble_rating bubble_50</item><item>ui_bubble_rating bubble_50</item></ratingClasses><reviewTitles><item>Best service and excellent food</item><item>Nice staff</item><item>Amazing Food</item><item>Excelente experience</item><item>Fine dining Vietnam style</item><item>Service is good</item><item>Best meal we’ve had in Vietnam!</item><item>Fantastic service and food</item><item>GOOD DAYS STAY ON C CENTRAL</item><item>Awesome food!</item></reviewTitles><reviewContents><item>It is the last day of our trip and we are really fortunate to come across with this restaurant. We got really good advice from the waitress, Bya who keep us in comfortabe. The food is excellent and we are definitely coming back!</item><item>They are good res with delious dishes, romantic atmosphere, cozy area, best staff- Blue. Thank for your help us take taxi under raining.</item><item>Going to this restaurant was an absolutely delightful experience. The food was incredible and very well presented. The pork belly and no escape chicken were delicious. Alice’s service was incredible, offering us a free entree as the one we wanted was sold out. Would definitely recommend this restaurant.</item><item>It is a very nice restaurant, with a fantástico food. Thanks yo Tom and Dung for their goos advices.</item><item>Lovely kind of a restaurant in the backpacker area of Saigon. Innovative food preparation and presentation. Loved the pork belly and the palate cleansing sorbet in between courses. Highly attentive professionally friendly staff. Would return again.</item><item>The receptionist and servers(Tom) here are very friendly and helpful! The location is also very convenient, near convenient store , bar</item><item>Our meal at Garlik was the last in Vietnam after a three week trip and I can confidently say that this was the best meal we’ve had! Garlik has a lovely interior and ambiance, owing to the live piano music. The staff were very personable and attentive. Our servers Bya and Betty made the visit particularly memorable. Finally and most importantly, the food was excellent! We all had the glazed pork belly - it was well seasoned, very tender and a good portion size. Highly recommended and well worth a visit if you’re in Ho Chi Minh.</item><item>Definitely the highlight of my food experience in Vietnam. The staff, especially Bya, were incredibly personable and attentive and provided an amazing customer experience. Furthermore, the food was delicious and extremely well-presented.Would recommend to all visiting Ho Chi Minh - personally I will be coming again!</item><item>Thanks for Stepan, Suy, Tom and Betty.
All of you are nice and friendly, warmed, I have good days on C central hotel during my vacation on Vietnam, wish you all good for everything.</item><item>I stayed in C Central Hotel and at the basement is the Garlik Restaurant.  

Food is awesome and the staff are very friendly!

Go Garlik!
Cheers!</item></reviewContents><usernames><item>nathanlee1121</item><item>geminips</item><item>ellatrev</item><item>Oscar E</item><item>christoph727</item><item>HuangErin123</item><item>psam208</item><item>mattsN7120QK</item><item>yin1015</item><item>Eranio S</item></usernames><userImages><item/><item/><item/><item/><item/><item/><item/><item/><item/><item/></userImages></reviews>