<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><reviews><codes><item>731313997</item><item>727755175</item><item>726527644</item><item>726409148</item><item>721885364</item><item>721505385</item><item>718600816</item><item>716173014</item><item>716000116</item><item>715877465</item></codes><dates><item>December 8, 2019</item><item>November 20, 2019</item><item>November 14, 2019</item><item>November 14, 2019</item><item>October 27, 2019</item><item>October 26, 2019</item><item>October 15, 2019</item><item>October 7, 2019</item><item>October 7, 2019</item><item>October 6, 2019</item></dates><ratingClasses><item>ui_bubble_rating bubble_50</item><item>ui_bubble_rating bubble_50</item><item>ui_bubble_rating bubble_50</item><item>ui_bubble_rating bubble_50</item><item>ui_bubble_rating bubble_30</item><item>ui_bubble_rating bubble_50</item><item>ui_bubble_rating bubble_50</item><item>ui_bubble_rating bubble_50</item><item>ui_bubble_rating bubble_50</item><item>ui_bubble_rating bubble_50</item></ratingClasses><reviewTitles><item>Great Tacos</item><item>Hidden Taco gem!!</item><item>Great food, mellow, friendly staffs and good drinks.</item><item>Perfect tacos night</item><item>The poutine is good, everything else not</item><item>Great food!</item><item>Hidden Gem in Saigon with unique food and ambiance</item><item>Awesome place, outstanding owner</item><item>I'll say these were the best tacos ever</item><item>A great pleasure</item></reviewTitles><reviewContents><item>Small place. Relaxed atmosphere. Bring cash. Most important, food was great. Location is a bit hidden, need to go around the left side of the building.</item><item>Stopped by with my fiancée for her bday.Looking for a cool spot to start the night and we weren’t disappointed.We ordered the Nachos and edamame guacamole to start. Guac is definitely on point!!This was followed up with 6 tacos... Decided to order the whole board.I finished up with an extra taco; the ox tongue which I thought was the best of the 6!!Thanks again Calvin for the birthday shots!!Definitely recommend trying the ox tongue!!</item><item>Great food, mellow, friendly staffs and good drinks.I went there with my boyfriend, even though we searched for the menu beforehand, we couldn’t believe that the food could be that pleasant until we taste the bacon and blue cheese edamame guacamole. I can’t recommend it enough. Other beautiful things are the Spicy Gochujang Chicken (super ), Kalbi Shredded Beef and Ox Tongue Barbacoa Tacos. Go and try it, you would totally in love.And of course, Calvin makes this place special when he is around!</item><item>In a few words : Good drinks, great atmosphere, perfect food.My girlfriend and I went there for a date night, and we could not be more happy : the staff is very friendly, the place is cosy, the tacos are sophisticated, generous and perfectly seasoned, spiced to perfection. Huge shout-out to the bacon and blue cheese edamame guacamole which was the stand out dish of the night.To sum up : El Camino is a tasteful place to hangout, managed by a caring chef with innovative ideas and attention to details. Bravo !</item><item>The poutine is good. Tacos are merely average and expensive, considering the location and ingredients. The margarita made my girlfriend and me ill. We only had one drink.</item><item>Such a nice place. Great food and good prices. These are the best Korean tacos I’ve ever had. Much recommended.</item><item>Delicious tacos (oxtail for the win!), environment and hip hop music, best experienced with friends. A great place to pre-game before a night out, or to enjoy a nightcap in a cozy setting with good friends. Very friendly owner. Nothing like it in the HCMC; it almost felt like I was in a hip restobar in Los Angeles’ Korea Town. Had a blast here eating late night tacos and downing a margarita. I also recommend the potato bombs as an appetizer.</item><item>Ive been coming here many times and the place is awesome. Great food, great atmosphere and easily worth the money for what you get.The owner is beyond friendly and makes sure the food is always top notch. Place isnt large so make a reservation. Its tricky to find, if your facing the building, go all the way to the left and walk down that passageway till you see it.</item><item>I'll say these were the best tacos never.
The flavours were just spot on.
I'll be back to sample more in future.
Highly recommended, BTW staff and the owner Calvin are awesome.</item><item>A great bar and restaurant and a nice vibe, staff and owner was super nice.It’s tucked away so has little Street noise and a full bar so can either drink or eat :)</item></reviewContents><usernames><item>PeteZuke</item><item>Justin M</item><item>Huong N</item><item>CharlesMaiLam</item><item>roaracle49</item><item>michelleloeken</item><item>959darrenj</item><item>DittyDoot</item><item>Sinh N</item><item>danmD5250KP</item></usernames><userImages><item/><item/><item/><item/><item/><item>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-l/06/48/84/3e/michelle-l.jpg</item><item/><item/><item>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-l/1a/f6/ec/3d/default-avatar-2020-1.jpg</item><item/></userImages></reviews>