<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><reviews><codes><item>737320675</item><item>736071457</item><item>734646466</item><item>734537054</item><item>734084988</item><item>733179517</item><item>732105941</item><item>729005170</item><item>727874484</item><item>723443739</item></codes><dates><item>January 6, 2020</item><item>January 1, 2020</item><item>December 25, 2019</item><item>December 24, 2019</item><item>December 22, 2019</item><item>December 17, 2019</item><item>December 11, 2019</item><item>November 26, 2019</item><item>November 20, 2019</item><item>November 3, 2019</item></dates><ratingClasses><item>ui_bubble_rating bubble_50</item><item>ui_bubble_rating bubble_50</item><item>ui_bubble_rating bubble_50</item><item>ui_bubble_rating bubble_50</item><item>ui_bubble_rating bubble_40</item><item>ui_bubble_rating bubble_40</item><item>ui_bubble_rating bubble_50</item><item>ui_bubble_rating bubble_50</item><item>ui_bubble_rating bubble_50</item><item>ui_bubble_rating bubble_40</item></ratingClasses><reviewTitles><item>One of the best Indian restaurants in Ho Chi Minh City</item><item>Brilliant evening</item><item>Impressive from all aspects, worth visiting. Good food and service</item><item>Great food and good location.</item><item>Very nice authentic Indian</item><item>Authentic Indian Taste</item><item>A welcome meal!</item><item>Excellent Indian Restaurant in Ho Chi Minh City / Saigon</item><item>Genuine Indian fare in Saigon</item><item>Very good curry</item></reviewTitles><reviewContents><item>We were referred to Tandoor by one of my friends who had recently visited and really liked it. We went out of curiosity one day and knew exactly why it was recommended so highly. The menu is hand-crafted, the presentation is impressive but what stands out is the customer service. The staff is super attentive, prompt and very efficient. The place is always in demand and a must-visit if you are craving for some Indian food in Ho Chi Minh City.</item><item>We were a group of 70 and the restaurant met all our expectations and beyond. The manager, Taj Mohamed, was brilliant and no request was too difficult for him. The food was delicious and the atmosphere has perfect. All round excellent evening.</item><item>The restaurant interiors are very nicely done and you immediately feel like eating there. It is one of the better Indian restaurants in HCMC. We went as part of our tour package so I am not sure about the prices but I am sure it would be on the higher side. The curries were a bit bland but the dal was good, paneer tikka was good. Overall enjoyed the meal and service was also quite fast. Would definitely recommend visiting.</item><item>Great food and good location. Lovey atmosphere and super selection of dishes very tasty at a reasonable price.</item><item>Very nice authentic Indian food restaurant close to the river. Cozy environment and superb service. 

Food very tasty but could have chosen an even more spice dish.</item><item>Authentic Indian Taste. Highly recommended for people who want to try Indian food for the first time. Having a dinner with listening to Bollywood songs, amazing atmosphere.</item><item>I spend a week in Ho Chi Minh City. Tandor provided the best overall experience of all restaurants that I ate at. The food was excellent. True comfort food for a weary traveler. Price and service were good as well. I ate at Tandor twice.</item><item>A really great Indian restaurant in Saigon / Ho Chi Minh City. Service very friendly and professional, the food exceptionally good and the prices reasonable, especially for such a high quality restaurant. I highly recommend this wonderful place to eat in Ho Chi Minh City / Saigon, Vietnam.</item><item>The four of us had dinner at Tandoor and were amazed not only with the number of items on offer but also the genuine Indian fare served to us, including fresh crispy tandoori rotis. The dal and tandoori dishes were just like the restaurants back home</item><item>Had a lovely meal here with my wife and friends. Excellent menu, very popular restaurant. Food was outstanding, ambiance excellent, very nice staff and reasonable. Definitely worth a visit.</item></reviewContents><usernames><item>s0ma</item><item>abiedawjeetours</item><item>harishbala</item><item>JamesBond89</item><item>sama985</item><item>buntyck</item><item>Mvbernard</item><item>shorexcursions</item><item>Nageshs</item><item>m0rayh</item></usernames><userImages><item/><item/><item/><item/><item/><item/><item/><item/><item/><item/></userImages></reviews>