<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><reviews><codes><item>756502297</item><item>750071668</item><item>749840441</item><item>749369228</item><item>748423185</item><item>747684451</item><item>747467175</item><item>746323870</item><item>743535862</item><item>739272224</item></codes><dates><item>June 2, 2020</item><item>March 9, 2020</item><item>March 8, 2020</item><item>March 5, 2020</item><item>February 29, 2020</item><item>February 25, 2020</item><item>February 24, 2020</item><item>February 20, 2020</item><item>February 7, 2020</item><item>January 15, 2020</item></dates><ratingClasses><item>ui_bubble_rating bubble_40</item><item>ui_bubble_rating bubble_50</item><item>ui_bubble_rating bubble_40</item><item>ui_bubble_rating bubble_50</item><item>ui_bubble_rating bubble_50</item><item>ui_bubble_rating bubble_50</item><item>ui_bubble_rating bubble_50</item><item>ui_bubble_rating bubble_40</item><item>ui_bubble_rating bubble_40</item><item>ui_bubble_rating bubble_20</item></ratingClasses><reviewTitles><item>A nice place to stop by</item><item>Tasty tacos</item><item>This place is a great little hole in the wall</item><item>Excellent burrito!</item><item>Very tasty</item><item>Nonla guys Vietnamese Taco on Bui Vien, District 1</item><item>Best taco</item><item>Very yummy take on Mexican food</item><item>Amazing burritos, just missing beans</item><item>NOT Tacos</item></reviewTitles><reviewContents><item>The service was great, the waitress that served me was attentive and cheerful. The food was pretty good for a vietnamese-mexican fusion cuisine. I ordered one of their Vietnamese style burritos which was satisfying and tasty. Also, it's a good place to eat at if you're on a budget.</item><item>Visited here one evening after reading good reviews. We paid 69,000 Dong for one meal of two tacos. My girlfriend had 2 tacos and I had 4, and we shared a plate of chips on the side for 39,000 Dong. A beer is 28,000 Dong.The food is very tasty and came out quickly. The staff are friendly and serve with a smile.Would recommend coming here.</item><item>This place is a great little hole in the wall with interesting food. Vietnamese Mexican fusion. I ended up getting a mango quesadilla and it was pretty damn tasty. It was a little small but I’m a fat American so of course it was. But other than that I highly recommend it. After I get used to eating meat again I will try their bun cha burrito. It sounds amazing.</item><item>my partner and I stopped by this place for a quick bite and it was delicious. cheap tasty food which I would happily eat again.</item><item>This is one of my favorites in Saigon. Usually I don't find fusion food very successful. However, the enchiladas, Burritos and Tacos with Vietnamese, Japanese and Korean flavours are very tasty.</item><item>A little gem hidden on the side alleys of Bui Vien's busy streets. A little mix of Spanish Tacos, Quesadillas, and Buritos with asian flair of Vietnamese, Korean, or Japanese infusion. Served by Minh, totally friendly (a little clumsy when he spilled beer on me) but he made it up with his warm and friendly attitude. Will definitely mark this on my map if I'm ever visiting Saigon again for a quick bite and relaxed atmosphere. Recommend to anyone who wants quick bite.</item><item>Came with my partner as we fancied something a bit different.Can honestly say the best taconive ever had ( I had the Vietnamese taco).The staff were super friendly as soon as you walk in you are greeted warmly.We made several visits here during our stay in Ho chi Minh City.</item><item>Very yummy take on Mexican food! We had the quesadillas with the combo which were super yummy. Wouldn’t say very authentic Mexican but I don’t think that’s their aim! Extremely yummy food and cocktails (cheap too) with friendly staff as well!</item><item>The burritos here and delicious. It's kind of fusian with their meat mixes being things like Vietnamese bun cha or korean spicy pork etc. Burritos themselves are reasonably small but great value for what you pay. The side of pickled onions and carrots is a nice touch and their spicy sauces are delicious if you want to turn up the heat a bit. Quick and friendly service too.The only downside is they don't have any sort of beans in any of their products which I think is a must have for burritos.</item><item>Taco wraps are peking duck wraps, NOT Tacos. also I would only have the beef, had the bun cha and it was not good, I'm vietnamese and thought this was a weird rendition.No salsa on anything and no cheese either. This was not good. I would not recommend.</item></reviewContents><usernames><item>donpapapalma</item><item>alexh11494</item><item>W605CLtonyh</item><item>nyleb2018</item><item>Ron20177</item><item>DerekY173</item><item>AweSam87</item><item>claudsbb</item><item>171traviss</item><item>yummyinmytummy88</item></usernames><userImages><item/><item/><item/><item>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-l/1a/f6/ee/db/default-avatar-2020-10.jpg</item><item/><item/><item/><item>https://media-cdn.tripadvisor.com/media/photo-l/1a/f3/d2/24/caption.jpg</item><item/><item/></userImages></reviews>