<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><reviews><codes><item>729595982</item><item>729385648</item><item>729373333</item><item>729355679</item><item>727839522</item><item>725460816</item><item>716640002</item><item>715965480</item><item>714131199</item><item>713785444</item></codes><dates><item>November 29, 2019</item><item>November 27, 2019</item><item>November 27, 2019</item><item>November 27, 2019</item><item>November 20, 2019</item><item>November 10, 2019</item><item>October 9, 2019</item><item>October 7, 2019</item><item>September 30, 2019</item><item>September 28, 2019</item></dates><ratingClasses><item>ui_bubble_rating bubble_50</item><item>ui_bubble_rating bubble_50</item><item>ui_bubble_rating bubble_50</item><item>ui_bubble_rating bubble_50</item><item>ui_bubble_rating bubble_50</item><item>ui_bubble_rating bubble_50</item><item>ui_bubble_rating bubble_50</item><item>ui_bubble_rating bubble_30</item><item>ui_bubble_rating bubble_50</item><item>ui_bubble_rating bubble_40</item></ratingClasses><reviewTitles><item>The best cocktail in saigon for sure</item><item>Drinking with friends</item><item>Favorite bar in HCMC</item><item>Saigon nightlife</item><item>Highly recommend</item><item>Another angle to see Saigon</item><item>You Should be here</item><item>It's fine</item><item>Best cocktail, nice view, good atmostphere</item><item>D place ^^</item></reviewTitles><reviewContents><item>Good cocktails from young talented bartender guys. Im just randomly talk about my tastes, they said they try to stole my heart from their drinks, and guess what, they did it.</item><item>cozy, comfy and relax for friends group. Beers have multi-choices for beer's lover to enjoy and discover new tastes. Cocktails are also good selections with fresh fruits from local. Great for friends after work, can gather and enjoy</item><item>the D is my favorite bar in Ho Chi Minh City.
There is good beer, good music, good interior, good people.</item><item>Best cocktail in Saigon &#129321;&#129321;&#129321; good place for meeting, dating or just enjoy good drinks to relax and chilling &#128526;&#128526;&#128526;</item><item>Really enjoyed my night here! Good drinks, good atmosphere and friendly staff. Suitable for chilling and chatting</item><item>Nice staff, good vibes, great view and superb cocktails. I had a great time spending the evening there. At first I was attracted by its open design of the rooftop bar and the craft beer on tap. But the staff introduce several cocktails for me...More</item><item>Placed in good location of Saigon, the D bar has nice view and simple decoration, especially it has very nice cocktails and many choices of draft beer and choices of liquor.
The D will bring you a fresh and relaxing feeling ...You can chill out...More</item><item>Basic little cocktail bar, cocktails were so so nothing very special. They also have a few local craft beers on tap. Nothing really stood out for me, especially as there are way better options on the same street.</item><item>Best cocktail i have ever tasted in HCMC and in the world, rooftop is very chill place, nice view and great to hang out with friends. I love the live music on Sunday night. Price is very affordable. I come here almost every weekend.</item><item>It was really out of a blue... didn't expect much... but place was nice... waitresses were a bit insistent to order right away. But cocktail was great. Just a bit sweet... I took the mother of the dragons. We happened to go there when they...More</item></reviewContents><usernames><item>Hoangphuong11</item><item>lifeforenjoy</item><item>609hayatoo</item><item>Ashley-ng11</item><item>Cy F</item><item>leungkk817</item><item>Ri N</item><item>TheIntrepidBeard</item><item>thaonhung2201</item><item>celesteorion</item></usernames><userImages><item/><item/><item/><item/><item/><item/><item/><item/><item/><item/></userImages></reviews>